audiotheme.com 2015-03-16

# Privacy Policy — AudioTheme

Your privacy is critically important to us.

At AudioTheme we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals.

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our [support team](https://audiotheme.com/contact/).

AudioTheme, LLC (“ **AudioTheme** “) operates a variety of websites including [audiotheme.com](http://www.audiotheme.com/), [support.audiotheme.com](http://make.audiotheme.com/), and [demo.audiotheme.com](https://demo.audiotheme.com/). It is AudioTheme’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, AudioTheme collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. AudioTheme’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how AudioTheme’s visitors use its website. From time to time, AudioTheme may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

AudioTheme also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on AudioTheme.com blogs or forums. AudioTheme only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog and forum commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to AudioTheme’s websites choose to interact with AudioTheme in ways that require AudioTheme to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that AudioTheme gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who create an account on [AudioTheme.com](http://www.audiotheme.com/) to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with AudioTheme – by purchasing a license for the AudioTheme Framework, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, AudioTheme collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with AudioTheme. AudioTheme does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

AudioTheme may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, AudioTheme may monitor the most popular product demos on the [AudioTheme.com Demo Site](https://demo.audiotheme.com/) or use spam screened by the Akismet service to help identify spam. AudioTheme may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, AudioTheme does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

AudioTheme may also collect theme usage data through our automatic update mechanism, which checks to insure you have the latest version of the AudioTheme Framework and/or Theme purchased. This process is necessary in order to provide you with a painless and consistent upgrade experience. You can opt out of receiving automatic updates to the latest version of the Framework and your theme by removing your license key in the AudioTheme settings.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

AudioTheme discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on AudioTheme’s behalf or to provide services available at AudioTheme’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using AudioTheme’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. AudioTheme will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, AudioTheme discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when AudioTheme believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of AudioTheme, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an AudioTheme account and have supplied your email address, AudioTheme may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with AudioTheme and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. AudioTheme takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. AudioTheme uses cookies to help AudioTheme identify and track visitors, their usage of AudioTheme website, and their website access preferences. AudioTheme visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using AudioTheme’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of AudioTheme’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If AudioTheme, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that AudioTheme goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of AudioTheme may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by AudioTheme and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, AudioTheme may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in AudioTheme’s sole discretion. AudioTheme encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Note, this Privacy Policy was derived from [Automattic’s version](http://automattic.com/privacy/), which is available under a [Creative Commons Sharealike](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/) license.

_Last updated on October 7, 2013 at 8:21 am_
